Next, we will look at this style, which is a style where the lower part of the chest is divided and the chest is turned, or even a style where the chest is cut.
We still compare this style with the round shape. After comparison, we found that the A-spleen is gone, but at the bottom of the B-spleen, there is a division line at the lower part of the chest.
The thoracic spine is gone, and it must have moved to this position, and there are more folds in this place. The B-spleen is gone, and the B-spleen needs to be eliminated.
When we encounter this style, how do we do it?
When there is a division passing through the throat, because we see that this division passes through the A-spleen and the B-spleen, right?
In this case, the A-spleen is temporarily transferred out, and the B-spleen is temporarily eliminated, so that the lower part of the chest is very flat, so that it is convenient for us to draw a division line, and then we do it in a 3D window.
Now I will show you the A-spleen.
In the 4th section, the
Crew's neck, we think B-spleen has a bigger hole.
Now it's first analyzed, and then it's measured again.
Let us watch the show for the next 3-d Nepalesewheel structure.
Here it is the Q-spleen, and what it is now?
Because the two curric reactors are not the same, the band doesn't need to be the same length, so we need the otherつp酸 masu quc total length.
First, we are products need the center of the structure, then Carotene is not listed in the D-spleen.
and keep it as a straight line.
Otherwise, it won't be easy to merge them.
It's the same when merging.
Okay, let's delete this.
Let's see, 118.3.
Then let's change it to 118.3.
The position of the BP point remains the same.
At this point, let's look again.
It's very flat below the contour line.
A flat surface is very suitable
for us to draw a separation line.
We can also adjust our waistline
to a natural arc.
Let's go back to the
separation line.
When we draw this separation line,
you should pay attention.
Generally speaking,
we need to go to the BP point
about 1.8 cm below.
This is the size of the lower chest.
Let's draw this arc.
Okay, let's look again at this point.
It's about 1.8 cm.
This is the same distance
as we want.
The front edge and the side seam
can be drawn according to the proportion
in the style chart.
Let's look at this point.
Okay, after the separation line is drawn,
we can cut it off directly.
After cutting it off,
we won't make any changes
to the next piece.
We will mainly make changes
to the upper section.
There is no arch on the upper section,
so the arch must be transferred
to this new position.
We still use the arch transfer method.
Press the Shift key
to select the edge of the arch.
Press the right mouse button
to rotate the arch.
Let's find the position of the transfer.
For example,
it is closer to the BP point now.
Closer to this point.
Then left-click to select the starting point of the arch.
Then move to the BP point.
Press the left mouse button again.
We move to the front center line.
We don't move to the front center line.
Then select the outer part
without the front center line.
Press the left mouse button.
Okay, let's select the moving mouse.
It's the arch of the arch.
Let's merge the arch.
Okay, at this time,
our arch
must be the part
where we don't accept the arch.
Okay, let's move the arch.
The amount of the arch
is not the amount of the arch,
but the amount of the fold.
So let's drag it down
to the edge of the arch.
At this time,
the original edge of the arch
that appeared just now
needs to be merged.
Let's delete it.
In this case,
we have completed
our arch transfer.
After the arch transfer,
this position
is actually not smooth.
So I need to use
the editor's far-fetched tool
to make it smooth.
So we want to fit the position
and do something about it.
Let's put it in the position
where we can see the large arch.
Okay,
we can see the large arch.
Let's create the same position
and delete the arch.
So we have created
the large arch,
and we can see
the smaller arch.
Right,
this position
is really smooth.
This is good.
Before,
we could delete
the arch of the arch.
We could delete
the rest of the lines
that appeared
during the drawing process.
Another thing
is that we can delete
so we can delete it as well.
Next, we're going to merge.
When merging,
if we
convert these two points to free-line points,
we'll merge.
When merging,
if you merge the top and bottom directly,
the extra value of the sum
will be evenly distributed.
In the picture,
the sum is not evenly distributed,
but is mainly concentrated in this position.
So in this position,
the other positions are equal.
Including the front and middle,
these points can also be equal.
Then,
the amount after the conversion
is mainly put in this place.
We see that it is not equal, right?
The remaining amount is the total amount.
Then we open the board and the free-line
symmetrically.
Next,
we merge the side gap into the merge.
After merging,
we open the 3D window.
We open this piece of paper.
Open the arrangement point.
Arrange it.
At the same time,
we print it.
It's easier to do.
Let's simulate.
Then our students may say,
why is there no fold?
Because it has been printed.
After printing,
the amount is held up,
so we remove the printing.
There will be a little fold,
but because we said before
that when the short-line and the long-line are merged,
we open it.
Then we make it 100%.
At this time,
we can see the fold.
If you think the fold is not enough,
what should we do?
I think the fold is too small.
It doesn't meet the effect I want.
Then what should we do?
Then it involves another way
of paper-like processing.
How to cut?
I need to use another function
in 3D.
Let's do it first.
For example,
my fold now points to the shoulder line.
Then I start from the shoulder line
and point to the starting point of the fold.
Okay,
press the left button of the mouse.
Then move the mouse.
At this time,
we will find that
the lower chest part has opened.
Right?
This adds a certain decorative fold.
After adding a decorative fold,
we still need to adjust it.
We need to use the tool of the edge curve.
Press the right button of the mouse to see the fold.
Press the right button of the mouse
to see the fold.
and make sure that
the fold is leveled.
Okay.
After adjusting the fold,
and then the shoulder line
should also be adjusted as well.
Because when cutting,
the shoulder line is no longer a straight line.
We need to use
the shape-to-fold curve
to adjust the fold. Then we can change it to the edge point.
Click on the point and line tool
Then turn these two points into a free-line point
These two points can also be turned into a free-line point
At this time, we are checking
We are checking
Because this ruler is still focused on the chest
We are checking other places
Has it changed
The front and the side of the ruler keep it the same
Then let its main fold focus on this place
Let's check again
At this time, we are checking
Its fold is larger than just now
Closer to the effect of our effect drawing
Let's increase the quality
This effect is closer to our style